Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Women's Rights Serials TAM.751
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- NOW Newsletter: National Organization for Women - Central New Jersey Chapter, Princeton, NJ, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- NOW NYC News: National Organization for Women / NOW - New York City, New York, NY, 1986-1987, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- NOW Washington State Newsletter: National Organization for Women, Tacoma, WA, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- NOW York Times: National Organization for Women / NOW New York, New York, NY, 1970, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- NOW York Woman: National Organization for Women, New York, NY, 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- NOW York Woman: National Organization for Women, New York, NY, 1970-1973, 1978-1985 (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
- NOW York Woman: National Organization for Women, New York, NY, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- NOW York Woman: Newsletter of the New York Chapter: National Organization for Women, New York, NY, 1970-1971, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 14-16, Box 17, Folder 7)
- NOW-NYS Action Report: National Organization for Women, Albany, NY, 1985-1986, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 8, Box 28, Folder 13)
- now...and then: National Organization for Women, Brooklyn, NY, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- NOW: The Rape Issue: National Organization of Women- Rape Prevention Committee, New York, NY, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Now'sletter: Seattle-National Organization for Women, Seattle, WA, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 9, Box 26, Folder 11)
- One-to-One Committee: National Organization for Women, New York, NY, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 18, Box 26, Folder 12)
- Organizer: National Organization for Women, Seattle, WA, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Other Woman: Other Woman Collective/The Canadian Feminist, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1972-1975 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Our Bodies! Our Choice!: FIT Publications/Fourth Internationalist Tendency Pamphlet, New York, NY, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- OURS: OURS, Inc., Little Rock, AR, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- P.S.: Prolifers for Survival, Erie, PA, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- P.S.: Prolifers for Survival, Chapel Hill, NC, 1980-1983 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Pandora: a Washington Women's News Journal: Pandora, Seattle, WA, 1971-1979 (Box 19, Folder 1-5)
- Papers in Women's Studies: University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, MI, 1974-1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- PAX: Women's International League for Peace and Freedom/Women's International League, New York, NY, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Pedestal: Pedestal, Vancouver, Canada, 1972-1975 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- PLUS: Women's Press, Toronto, Canada, circa 1970s (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Politics of Sexuality in Capitalism: Red Rag Collective, London, England, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Preventing Sexual Harassment: A Fact Sheet for Employees: Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., Washington, DC, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Pride and Prejudice: Pride and Prejudice, Canada, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Profilers for Survival: Profilers for Survival, Chapel Hill, NC, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Progressive Woman: Corson Publishing Inc., Middlebury, IN, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Propaganda: A Worksheet: Women's Studies College/Octographics, Buffalo, NY, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Quest: A Feminist Quarterly: Quest: A Feminist Quarterly, Washington, DC, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Quicksilver Times: Quicksilver Times, Inc. / Washington Independent Publishing Co., Washington, DC, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 6, Box Shared Tamiment 053, Folder 17)
- Rape Line: National Organization for Women - New York, New York, NY, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Rape: Research, Action, Prevention: University of Alabama - Center for Correctional Psychology, Tuscaloosa, AL, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Red Rag: Red Rag / Febedge Printers, London, England, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Referendum Controlo Il Divorzio: Edizioni "La Fiaccola", Catania, Italy, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Report of the Commission to the Council on the Application of the Principle of Equal Pay for Men and Women in Denmark, Ireland and the United Kingdom: Commission of the European Communities, Brussels, Belgium, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Report of the Women and Employment Group: United Nations Decade For Women, London, England, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Reporter: Viewpoints, Buffalo, NY, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Research Series Report: Working Women's Institute, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Revolution / evolution: Department of Women's Studies, New York University, New York, NY, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Revolution Youth: Solidarity Youth and Student Bulletin, Chicago, IL, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Revolution/evolution: Undergraduate Women's Studies Program at NYU, New York, NY, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Revolutionary Worker - Special Magazine Section - Women Are Not Incubators: RCP Publications, Chicago, IL, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Sage-Femme: Gainesville Women's Health Center, Gainesville, FL, 1977 (Box Shared Tamiment 053, Folder 18)
- Schlesinger Library Newsletter: Radcliffe College, Cambridge, MA, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Second Coming: Austin Women's Liberation, Austin, TX, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 20, Box 20, Folder 2)
- Second Opinion: Coalition for the Medical Rights of Women, San Francisco, CA, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Second Page: Second Page, San Francisco, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Second Page: Second Page, San Francisco, CA, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Second Page: Second Page, San Francisco, CA, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Second Wave: Second Wave / Mother Jones Press, Baltimore, MD, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Sex, Family and the New Right: New England Free Press, Somerville, MA, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Sexism is Served a la the Arts: Alliance of Women for Equality, Maplewood, NJ, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Sister: West Coast Feminist Newspaper: Radical Therapy Collective, Venice, CA, circa 1970s (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Sister Advocate: Oklahoma Feminist Enterprises, Inc. / Sister Advocate, Oklahoma City, OK, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Sister Courage: Sister Courage, Inc., Allerton, MA, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Sister Lode: Women's Education Division of New Mexico REEF, Albuquerque, NM, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 26, Box 27, Folder 1)
- Sisterhood ... For Personhood: National Organization for Women, Wolcott, VT, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Sisterlife: Feminists for Life of America: Feminists for Life of America, Kansas City, MO, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Sojourner: Sojourner, Cambridge, MA, 1976-1977, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Sojourner: The Women's Forum: Sojourner, Jamaica Plain, MA, 1992, 1995, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Sourceline: Alaska Women's Resource Center, Anchorage, AK, 1976-1979 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- South Carolina WEAL Newsletter: South Carolina WEAL, Columbia, SC, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Spokeswoman: Washington Women's News Service, Falls Church, VA, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Status Report: Commission on the Status of Women Fund, Inc., New York, NY, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Struggles of Women are the Struggles of Us All!: International Women's Day March 8, 1974: Revolutionary Union / Vietnam Veterans Against the War / People's Voice / Attica Brigade / International Women's Day Committee, Chicago, IL (Box 7, Folder 2)
- This is Us: Women and Work: This is Us Collective/Women's Newsletter Collective, Lansing, MI, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Through the Looking Glass: Through the Looking Glass, Philadelphia, PA, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Title VII Report: Professional & Technical Programs, Inc., New York, NY, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Together: UCLA Women, Los Angeles, CA, 1974, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Top Stories: Top Stories / Hallwalls, Buffalo, NY, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Towards a Science of Women's Liberation: Red Rag Collective, London, England, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Triple Jeopardy: Third World Women's Alliance, New York, NY, 1971-1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Triple Jeopardy: Third World Women's Alliance, New York, NY, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Union W.A.G.E.: Union Women's Alliance to Gain Equality, Berkeley, CA, 1974-1976 (Box 21, Folder 4, Box Shared Tamiment 053, Folder 15)
- Union W.A.G.E.: Union Women's Alliance to Gain Equality, San Francisco, CA, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Union W.A.G.E.: Women's Alliance to Gain Equality/Waller Press, San Francisco, CA, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Update: Seattle Reproductive Rights Alliance, Seattle, WA, circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Vindicacion Feminista: Ediciones de Feminismo, Barcelona, Spain, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Vote: Women's Freedom League, London, England, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Votes for Women:, London, England, 1907-1908 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Vrouwen: Maandblad van de Nederlandse Vrouwenbeweging, Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- We Have Seen you There: Glad Day Press, Syracuse, NY, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- WHAM! Frontlines: Women's Health Action and Mobilization, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 13, Box 27, Folder 2)
- What the Florence Crittenton Home Does for Girls: Board of Directors of the Florence Crittenton Home, Mobile, AL, circa 1950s (Box 7, Folder 14)
- WhatNOW: National Organization for Women, New York, NY, 2005-2010 (Box 21, Folder 7, Box 27, Folder 3)
- Wifebeating: New England Free Press, Somerville, MA, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- WIN News: Women's International Network, Lexington, MA, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Windhaven: Atlanta Press, Seattle, WA, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Windsor Woman: Windsor Woman Newspaper, Windsor, Ontario, Canada, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Woman: The Majority Report: Woman: The Majority Report, La Jolla, CA, circa 1970s (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Woman Citizen: Woman Citizen Corporation, New York, NY, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Woman News: Commission on the Status of Women at Wayne, Detroit, MI, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Woman News: Women's Focus / Womanews, New York, NY, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Woman Newsletter: api press, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Woman's World: Woman's World, New York, NY (?), 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Woman's World: Woman's World, New York, NY, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- WomaNews: Women's Focus, New York, NY, 1985-1989 (Box 21, Folder 10, Box 28, Folder 12)
- Womankind: Chicago Women's Liberation Union, Chicago, IL, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- WomanScope: WomanScope Enterprises, Baltimore, MD, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Women: A Journal of Liberation: Women: A Journal of Liberation, Inc., New York, NY, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 1-7, Box 7, Folder 24-25)
- Women: A Journal of Liberation: Women: A Journal of Liberation, Inc., Berkeley, CA, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Women: A Journal of Liberation: Women: A Journal of Liberation, Inc., Baltimore, MD, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 23, Box 27, Folder 5)
- Women & Struggle in Iran: Women's Commission of the Iranian Students Association in the US, Chicago, IL, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Women Against Pornography Newsreport: Women's Liberation Writing Collective, Inc., New York, NY, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Women are People: Women are People, Cambridge, England, circa 1970s (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Women Artists in Revolution Newsletter: Women Artists in Revolution, New York, NY, circa 1970s (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Women Artists News: Midmarch Associates, New York, NY, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Women Artists Newsletter: Midmarch Associates, New York, NY, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Women Can.: Women Can., Vancouver, Canada, circa 1970s (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Women Employed: Women Employed, Chicago, IL, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Women in American Society: Radical America, Cambridge, MA, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Women in China Today: All-China Democratic Women's Federation, China, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Women in Humor: YWCA of New York City / Association of Comedy Artists, New York, NY, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Women Library Workers Journal: Women Library Workers, Berkeley, CA, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Women of the World: Women's International Democratic Federation, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Women Today: Today Publications & News Service, Washington, DC, 1971, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Women United: Women United for Action, New York, NY, 1973-1975 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Women Who Work: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Women Workers: International Socialists, Somerville, MA, circa 1960s (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Women Workers: The Forgotten Third of the Working Class: International Socialists, New York, NY, circa 1960s (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Women, Work, and Globalization in Late 20th Century Capitalism: Asian Women Immigrants in the United States: Department of Comparative American Cultures Washington State University, Pullman, WA, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Women: The Longest Revolution: New England Free Press, Boston, MA, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Women's Collective Press: McGill University Arts and Science Undergraduate Society, Montreal, Canada, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Women's Encampment For A Future of Peace & Justice: Resource Handbook: Women's Encampment For A Future of Peace & Justice, Seneca, NY, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Women's Heritage Calendar and Almanac: Women's Heritage Series / Graphic Communications Consultants, Santa Monica, CA, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Women's Journal: Isis International/Committee for Asian Women, Rome Italy, Kowloon, Hong Kong, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Women's Liberation: Women's Union Child Care Collective, New York, NY, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 12, Box Shared Tamiment 053, Folder 16)
- Women's Liberation Newsletter: Women's Center, Los Angeles, CA, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Women's Liberation: A Communist View: October League (Marxist-Leninist), Chicago, IL, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Women's Newspaper: Women's Newspaper, London, England, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Women's Page: Women's Page, San Francisco, CA, 1970, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Women's Political Times: National Women's Political Caucus, Washington, DC, 1979-1981, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 9, Box 28, Folder 14)
- Women's Press: Women's Press, Eugene, Or, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Women's Review of Books: Women's Review, Inc., Wellesley, MA, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Women's Street Theater: People's Press, San Francisco, CA, circa 1970s (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Women's Studies International: Feminist Press, Old Westbury, NY, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Women's Studies Newsletter: Feminist Press / The National Women's Studies Association, Old Westbury, NY, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 16, Box 27, Folder 8)
- Women's Studies Newsletter: Women's Education Advisory Committee // Workers' Educational Association, London, England, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Women's Studies Quarterly: Feminist Press / The National Women's Studies Association, College Park, MD, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Women's Way: Plain View Press, Austin, TX, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Womens Franchise: John Edward Francis, London, England, 1907 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Womens Voice: Socialist Worker Printers and Publishers Ltd., London, England, 1973-1976 (Box 23, Folder 3, Box 9, Folder 19)
- WONAAC National Newsletter: Women's National Abortion Action Coalition, Washington, DC, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- WONAAC Newsletter: Women's National Abortion Action Coalition, New York, NY, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Working Mother: Maternal Information Services, Inc., New York, NY, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Working Women and their Organizations: Union WAGE Educational Committee, Berkeley, CA, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Working Women Organization Newsletter: Working Women Organization, Zaman Colony, Pakistan, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- WREE-View of Women for Racial and Economic Equality: Women of the World / WREE, New York, NY, 1977, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- WREE-View of Women for Racial and Economic Equality: Women of the World / WREE, New York, NY, 1983-1992 (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
- Wree-View: Bulletin of Women for Racial and Economic Equality: Women for Racial and Economic Security, New York, NY, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- WREE-View of Women for Racial and Economic Equality: Women of the World / WREE, Chicago, IL, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 9)